spotlightstories.co 2019-04-03

# Spotlight - Restoring your faith in humanity

Effective as of July 18, 2018.

This Privacy Policy explains how Shareably Media, LLC (“ **Shareably** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”) collects, uses and shares your personal information if you use our website at shareably.net or any other Shareably website to which this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, our “ **Website** ”). 

**Table of Contents**

Personal Information We Collect

How We Use Your Personal Information

How We Share Your Personal Information

Your Choices

Cookies and Similar Technologies

Other Important Privacy Information

How to Contact Us

Notice to European Users

**Personal Information We Collect**

**Information you give us.** We may collect your name, email address and other information about you through the Website or otherwise when you request information, respond to surveys, participate in market research activities, report a problem with the Website, receive customer support or otherwise correspond with us. We may also collect other personal information from you that is not specifically mentioned in this Privacy Policy from time to time, but if we do we will use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Information automatically collected.** Our servers and third party service providers may automatically record certain information about how you use the Website and the device you use to access it, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, device and browser type, approximate geographic location (e.g., city or town), referring website, operating system, unique device identifiers, unique application and advertising identifiers, the pages or features of the Website that you browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, the frequency with which you use the Website, the links that you click on or use, and other statistics. We collect this information in server logs and by using cookies and similar tracking technologies. See our Cookie Policy for more information. 

Sensitive personal information. We ask that you not provide to us any sensitive personal information (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin; political opinions, religion or other beliefs; health, biometrics or genetic characteristics; criminal background or union membership) through the Website or otherwise, but if you do, you must consent to our use of this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

We use your personal information for the following purposes and as otherwise described to you in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection: 

**To provide the Website.** We use your personal information: 

  * to provide, operate and improve the Website;
  * to communicate with you regarding the Website, including by sending you announcements, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * to better understand your needs and interests, and personalize your experience with the Website; and
  * to respond to your Website-related requests, questions and feedback.

**For research and development.** We use information automatically collected and other information to analyze trends, administer the Website, analyze users’ movements around the Website, gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, improve the Website and develop new products and services. 

**To send you marketing communications.** We may send you promotions or other marketing communications but you may opt out of receiving them as described in the Opt out of marketing section below. 

**To provide you with advertising.** We may use your personal information to serve ads on the Website or on third party sites and to tailor ads to your interests and browsing history. See our Cookie Policy for more information. 

**To create anonymous data.** We may create aggregated and other anonymous data from our users’ information. We make personal information into anonymous data by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable. We may use this anonymous data and share it with third parties to understand and improve our products and services and for other lawful business purposes. 

**For compliance, fraud prevention and safety.** We may use your personal information as we believe appropriate to (a) investigate violations of and enforce our Terms of Use; (b) protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims); and (c) protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity. 

**For compliance with law.** We may use your personal information as we believe appropriate to (a) comply with applicable laws, lawful requests and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities; and (b) where permitted by law in connection with a legal investigation. 

**With your consent.** In some cases we may ask for your consent to collect, use or share your personal information, such as when required by law or our agreements with third parties. 

**How We Share your Personal Information**

We do not share your personal information with third parties without your consent, except in the following circumstances:

**Affiliates.** We may share your personal information with parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates for use consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Service providers.** We may share your personal information with third party companies and individuals as needed for them to provide us with services that help us with our business activities and to provide the Website (such as customer support, hosting and storage, website analytics, email delivery, marketing/advertising, database management services and legal and other professional advice). These third parties will be given limited access to your personal information that is reasonably necessary for them to provide their services.

**Compliance, fraud prevention, safety.** We may disclose your personal information as we believe appropriate to government or law enforcement officials or private parties for the purposes described above under the following sections: For compliance, fraud prevention and safety and For compliance with law.

**Business transfers.** We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our business or assets, including your personal information, in connection with a business deal (or potential business deal) such as a corporate divestiture, merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy or dissolution.

**Your Choices**

**Opt out of marketing.** You may opt out of marketing-related emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the email. You may continue to receive Website-related and other non-marketing emails.

**Opt out of advertising.** See our Cookie Policy for details on how to limit targeted advertising based on your information.

**Cookies and Similar Technologies**

We may allow service providers and other third parties to use cookies and other tracking technologies to track your browsing activity over time and across the Website and third party websites. For more details, see our Cookie Policy. Some Internet browsers may be configured to send "Do Not Track" signals to the online services that you visit. We currently do not respond to "Do Not Track" or similar signals. To find out more about "Do Not Track," please visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](https://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

**Other Important Privacy Information**

**Third party sites and services** The Website may contain links to other websites and services operated by third parties. These links are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third party. We do not control third party websites, applications or services, and are not responsible for their actions. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding their collection, use and sharing of your personal information. We encourage you to read their privacy policies to learn more. If you allow a third party service to access your user content in the Website, you do so at your own risk. 

**Security.** The security of your personal information important to us. We take a number of organizational, technical and physical measures designed to protect the personal information we collect. However, security risk is inherent in all internet and information technologies and we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your personal information. We will comply with applicable laws and regulations requiring that we notify you in the event your personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of our security measures. 

**International data use.** We are headquartered in the United States and have affiliates and service providers in other countries, and your personal information may be collected, used and stored in the United States or other locations outside of your home country. Privacy laws in the locations where we handle your personal information may not be as protective as the privacy laws in your home country. 

**Children.** The Website is not directed at, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from, anyone under the age of 16. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16, we will promptly delete that information. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.** We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will post them on the Site and indicate the effective date of the change. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by email or through the Website. 

**How to Contact Us**

Shareably Media, LLC  
2263 Ashbourne Drive  
San Ramon, CA 94583  

**Notice to European Users**

The following applies to individuals in the European Economic Area.

**Controller.** Shareably Media, LLC is the controller of your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy for purposes of European data protection legislation.

**Legal bases for processing.** The legal bases of our processing of your personal information are described in the table below. 

**Processing purpose** (click link for details) | **Legal basis**  
---|---  
To provide the Website | You have entered a contract with us and we need to use your personal information to provide services you have requested or take steps that you request prior to providing services.   
For research and development

To send you marketing communications

To provide you with advertising

To create anonymous data

For compliance, fraud prevention and safety

| These processing activities constitute our legitimate interests. We consider and balance the potential impact on your rights before we process your personal information for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal information for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).  
For compliance with law | Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations.  
With your consent | Processing is based on your consent. Where we rely on your consent you have the right to withdraw it anytime in the manner indicated in the Website.  
To share your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy | This sharing constitutes our legitimate interests, and in some cases may be necessary to comply with our legal obligations.  
  
**Retention.** Generally, we retain your personal information for as long as necessary to process your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

**Your rights.** European data protection laws give you certain rights regarding your personal information. You may ask us to take the following actions in relation to your personal information that we hold: 

  * **Access.** Provide you with information about our processing of your personal information and give you access to your personal information.
  * **Correct.** Update or correct inaccuracies in your personal information.
  * **Delete.** Delete your personal information.
  * **Transfer.** Transfer a machine-readable copy of your personal information to you or a third party of your choice.
  * **Restrict.** Restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * **Object.** Object to our reliance on our legitimate interests as the basis of our processing of your personal information that impacts your rights.

You may submit these requests by email to [hi@shareably.net](mailto:hi@shareably.net) or our postal address provided above. We may request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and process your request. Applicable law may require or permit us to decline your request. If we decline your request, we will tell you why, subject to legal restrictions. If you would like to submit a complaint about our use of your personal information or response to your requests regarding your personal information, you may contact us or submit a complaint to the data protection regulator in your jurisdiction. You can find your data protection regulator [here](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm). 

**Personal Data Export.** If we export your personal information from the European Economic Area to a country outside of it and are required to apply additional safeguards to that personal information under European data protection legislation, we will do so. Such safeguards may include applying the European Commission model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries described [here](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/model-contracts-transfer-personal-data-third-countries_en#international-data-transfers-using-model-contracts). Please contact us for further information about any such transfers or the specific safeguards applied.
